They are currently in our custody.
Their lawyers are appealing
for mitigating circumstances,
arguing that, in the end,
they helped dismantle
the Concordat and La Morte Bianca.
Maybe she just turned your adventure
business into a real adventure?
Mikoy, I have no problem with adventure.
But Chiara is different.
Whenever I take her as my tour guide,
I feel like I'm in
a permanent danger zone!
I thought you wanted to know what
really happened to Mikoy and Chiara.
Look how big it is!
So, assuming you catch
a fish in the river…
Like sashimi, like in Japan.
-Rhamboy.
-Right?
-What are you doing?
-Aunt Tess.
I'm vlogging.
What are you doing
with that enormous fish?
At least I'm not boring!
You need something new every now and then.
Not something boring,
not something that's always the same.
Wait. Why Albay?
Plus, their food is so good.
You know, laing,
-inangat.
-Inangat.
-Inangat!
-Yummy!
-Wow!
You two are really in sync, huh.
Did you practice that?
-Hungry.
-We're just hungry.
You two!
He inherited a piece of land
from his parents.
The only reason he's in Cebu
is because of Ma'am Tess.
But the truth is, he's a true-blue Oragon.
And it's probably traumatic
for them to return to Cebu
after everything that happened.
While in Bicol, his territory,
What kind of future
would Mikoy have there?
Magayon! Don't be shy!
Come out! My lovely goddess!
Clear away the clouds
My love!
Just give me
That beautiful smile!
Magayon!
Okay, good morning, everyone! Welcome!
Today, we'll show you
one of Bicol's greatest prides.
The art of abaca weaving!
Because iba ka. You're different.
There!
So, here we are.
Most people think this is just a rope.
But no, that is very, very wrong.
This is where bags, mats, hats,
and wall art all begin.
And sometimes, it's even
the cause of marital fights
because they picked the wrong color…
curtains!
The fibers are extracted
from the abaca plant.
Those are the plants you see behind us.
See?
You thought they were
just banana trees, didn't you?
But they're actually abaca plants.
But we're still not sure.
Because it's just a-"baka" maybe.
After that, it's dried under the sun.
Once it's dry,
it's cleaned, sorted, and graded
depending on its thickness and quality.
It's just like a beauty pageant.
Of course, there's
a first runner-up and a winner!
Of course, this is what it will look like.
See? Isn't it beautiful?
It's also very soft.
And that's not all.
It can also be made into fans.
For sweaty people like me.
And these are for you, too,
since you're all sweating now.
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, finally!
We've arrived at one
of Bicol's top products!
Pili nuts!
The finest handpicked nuts!
But before anything else,
we need to use this first,
so we can get the…
the chosen heart.
Who wants one?
So, who wants one?
With his profile, we know that
even though he's just starting out,
we know that with his resourcefulness,
he'll be able to get back
on his feet quickly.
Just like a universal charger.
You're right! Correct!
Um…
Well, I think Mikoy and Chiara
are the happiest they've ever been.
They've overcome
the biggest challenge of their lives.
And now, they have the chance to live
a normal and happy life.
So I'm certain
that every moment of their lives,
they'll be filled with happiness and love.
Wait, I have a feeling
something's going on.
I'm a senator. Why am I standing?
-Yes, sorry. My apologies.
-Get up from there.
Dekyo! Ka Pepe! Come on, let's eat here!
Hey, he said let's eat.
It's okay. We're still working on a play.
We have a three-on-three later.
Wow, impressive.
You sure?
We're good!
Is this idiot really angry?
Am I the one who should apologize to him?
If you don't want
to talk to me, then don't.
Hey, stay here for a while! Let's chat!
It's like they're different people now!
Come on. Don't be shy.
And he's really talking
to someone else while I'm here.
I admit that I did something wrong.
But for everything to be blamed on me…
Should I break his pinky
so he'll learn his lesson?
Do you want to have lunch later?
No, it's okay.
Let's just meet after work.
Hey, come on!
What are you doing there?
What kind of strategy is that?
This is the triangle offense.
I know that!
Was what I did really that bad?
I'm really getting annoyed with Mikoy.
You're the one giving me
the cold treatment?
What if I dunked your head
in a bucket of ice?
So annoying.
He's getting on my nerves.
Fine, if that's what he wants--
You're back?
Do you need something?
Nothing. Just my coffee.
Because I enjoy having coffee
while using the bathroom.
We'll talk later when I get home, okay?
We'll have a long chat!
Chiara, let's talk.
I don't want to.
You're dead!
Mom! Let's walk together.
You, Mikoy.
Why are you and Chiara
not going to work together?
Why did she leave first?
It's so early.
You're still denying it.
I know you guys have a problem.
We had an argument yesterday.
Why?
She's so stubborn.
So irresponsible.
She didn't even think that it's me
who recommended her to Sir Pandoy.
I feel responsible.
I'll be embarrassed.
Have you guys talked about why
she's acting like that?
Our voices started to rise as we argued.
How about earlier, was her tone the same?
See?
See? I knew it.
You're sulking too much.
You could've solved it earlier.
Of course, I'm still annoyed.
Is this not the life we imagined?
Now, it seems like
she's sabotaging everything.
Is she giving up?
She doesn't want this anymore?
Is this life too simple for her?
Son, instead of telling me that,
why don't you talk to her?
Is he still not talking to you?
Still ignoring you?
Yes, and this is actually
our longest fight ever.
Usually, we don't sleep
until we've sorted things out.
What did you tell him?
And what exactly did you guys fight about?
Not much.
What do you mean "not much"?!
Mikoy of all people?
Get angry over nothing?
Giving you the cold shoulder over nothing?
Well, I said I'm not a boring person.
Dear, tell me the whole story.
Give me all the details
if you want advice from me.
Not just half of the information.
If that's the case,
then just call on the radio.
Well, there's a…
problem at work.
I became a little stubborn.
A little bit.
A little bit?
It's Mikoy who recommended me
for this job.
Why did you have to act up?
Maybe because I'm bored.
Are you sure you're just bored?
Wow, in fairness to this…
smuggled phone,
the quality is really good.
I can feel the depth of your sigh.
Your sigh that's as deep
as the Pacific Ocean.
Okay, if not because of being bored,
maybe because I feel like I'm stuck.
There you go!
I'm happy.
It's just…
He seems like he doesn't have a plan.
Plan about what?
You have to understand Chiara's situation.
Her parents are in prison.
Think about the frustration
of being alone without your family.
No siblings.
Just alone.
But I'm here.
I know,
but it's inevitable for her to feel
that she's alone in this new life.
A fresh and new life
with only the two of you.
Son, here's the question.
What will you do to reassure her?
Right?
What decision will you make
for her to not feel lonely?
So that you two are a real family.
There! Smile!
Pose like this!
Your pictures are so cute!
I'll just get off, please.
It's so scary.
No, you can do it!
I believe in you.
You have to believe in yourself too.
I won't invalidate
that feeling of yours because it's real.
Your feelings are real.
You just have to overcome it
-Okay.
-and embrace it.
-Okay? You can do it.
-Okay.
-We'll count together, okay?
-On three.
-Slowly, okay?
I told you, you can do it!
Water? Or do you want to take a rest?
It's okay. We might be late
and miss the sunset.
It's fine. I have an idea
so we can go faster.
Oh no, it's okay. It's really okay.
-It's alright, so we can go faster.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, no worries.
-Thank you!
-Okay, watch your step.
It's a little slippery over here.
Yes, sir.
The lunch are prepared for the ATV guests.
Yes, Sir Pandoy.
Yes, sir. I'm expecting it already.
Yes.
Goodbye.
-Ma'am Den. Ma'am Den.
-Yes, Mikoy?
Can I talk to Sir Pandoy?
We weren't able to talk last time.
I want to say sorry on behalf of Chiara.
You know, she's from Prague
and has family problems.
What are you talking about?
They already talked earlier.
-Sir! Sir Pandoy, can we talk?
-Chiara.
About what?
Yes! Chiara went there
and asked for forgiveness.
And she was given another chance.
Really?!
Huh?
Is Sir Pandoy sure?
You said it yourself,
it's her first time in this kind of life.
She might get bored, right?
I also told her
that if she has any suggestions
that is good for the ATV, she can tell me.
We are open to any changes.
You know, I'm impressed by Chiara.
I'm sure she'll go a long way
in this business.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll personally thank Sir Pandoy
for giving Chiara a second chance.
Except Hitler.
Makes sense!
Okay, I'll go ahead.
-Okay.
-Sir might scold me.
-Bye!
-Take care.
I have good news.
Chiara.
The thing is…
Something happened to Mikoy.
What is it?
He's in the ecopark,
at the top of the mountain.
-Chiara…
-Chiara!
Chiara!
I'm coming, Mikoy.
What is happening to you?
Mikoy!
Mikoy?
Mikoy.
Mikoy, are you okay?
What is this for? What happened?
I'm not good with words.
All I know is that
this story started
when I was searching for something.
Searching for an opportunity
to help my family.
For a better life.
An opportunity to leave poverty behind.
Then I met you.
Unbelievable!
Too beautiful.
Too wealthy.
And worst of all,
the daughter of a mafia boss.
So many secrets,
things to hide.
You know what?
If I gambled,
I never would've bet on us surviving
all that we've been through.
even if we just stare out the window,
being bored.
I don't even care
if we have to jump out of a helicopter
or in the river.
I don't care if a bomb hits me right now.
It doesn't matter if the whole world
is mad at you.
I will face them all for you.
Ms. Chiara Valtrovi.
You are my greatest adventure.
And the greatest love of my life.
You are the real Pinagpala.
Mr. Mikoy Pinagpala, I will marry you.
I will be with you until my last breath.
That's why I'm so grateful
for accepting me.
But I don't think they would love
to go back and serve the agency.
We can convince them.
We can use Chiara's parents.
In exchange, we can release the people
that are important to Chiara.
Seriously, are you really going on a date?
Who is this? A person
you matched with online?
Bok, to be honest,
Wait, who is it? Do I know the person?
Agent Alex!
How are you?
Is there a problem?
You miss me, don't you?
Agent Alex!
Right, why did you call?
I just wanted to tell you that…